Today, we are announcing Wave 2 of Microsoft 365 Copilot.
오늘 Microsoft 365 Copilot 2차 출시를 발표합니다.
You can think of Copilot as the UI for AI.
Copilot은 AI의 UI라고 생각하면 됩니다.
It's about bringing the web plus work plus pages together as the new AI system.
웹과 업무, 페이지를 모두 새로운 AI 시스템으로 통합하는 것입니다.
Pages is a dynamic, persistent canvas designed for multiplayer AI collaboration.
페이지는 멀티플레이어 AI 협업을 위해 디자인된 동적이고 지속적인 캔버스입니다.
You now want to turn this simple response into a page.
이제 이 간단한 응답을 페이지로 바꾸고 싶습니다.
Here, you can keep working on your own with colleagues or with Copilot.
여기에서는 동료나 Copilot과 함께 혼자서 작업을 계속할 수 있습니다.
BizChat turns your organizational content into a rich database of information and insight,
BizChat은 조직의 콘텐츠를 풍부한 정보와 통찰력의 데이터베이스로 전환합니다.
where all of your data comes together.
모든 데이터가 하나로 모이는 곳입니다.
Web data, work data, and line of business data right in the flow of your work
웹 데이터, 업무 데이터, 사업부 데이터를 업무 흐름에 바로 적용
will start by pivoting from web to work.
웹에서 직장으로 전환하는 것으로 시작합니다.
Your coworker had an introductory two-hour meeting with the customer last week,
귀하의 동료는 지난 주에 고객과 2시간 동안 소개 회의를 가졌습니다.
so from right here in Pages, they asked Copilot to reference the recording of that meeting
그래서 바로 여기 Pages에서 그들은 Copilot에게 그 회의의 녹음을 참조하도록 요청했습니다.
and insert a bulleted list of the requirements.
그리고 요구 사항을 요점으로 나열해 보세요.
In seconds, Copilot was able to synthesize the discussion
몇 초 만에 Copilot은 토론 내용을 종합할 수 있었습니다.
and give your team the key takeaways.
팀에 주요 내용을 알려주세요.
Now, we all rely on information from the web to do our jobs,
이제 우리 모두는 웹의 정보에 의존하여 업무를 수행합니다.
but where work really happens is in Microsoft 365.
하지만 실제로 작업이 이루어지는 곳은 Microsoft 365입니다.
We are excited to announce Copilot in Excel with Python.
Python을 사용하여 Excel에서 Copilot을 발표하게 되어 기쁩니다.
Copilot opens up a new workspace.
Copilot은 새로운 작업 공간을 열어줍니다.
It shows a preview of what it's reasoning over,
그것은 무엇에 대해 추론하고 있는지 미리 보여줍니다.
creates a plan to analyze it in a way that is immediately useful,
즉시 유용한 방식으로 분석할 계획을 수립합니다.
and executes it by running and writing Python code.
Python 코드를 실행하고 작성하여 실행합니다.
PowerPoint is where people go to create and tell a story.
파워포인트는 사람들이 스토리를 만들고 전달하는 곳입니다.
Introducing Narrative Builder.
내러티브 빌더를 소개합니다.
With Copilot and PowerPoint's new Narrative Builder,
Copilot과 PowerPoint의 새로운 내러티브 빌더를 사용하여
you are in creative control.
당신은 창조적 통제력을 갖고 있습니다.
It starts with a draft outline where you can reorder the flow,
흐름을 재정렬할 수 있는 초안 개요로 시작합니다.
delete topics you don't want, or add new ones,
원하지 않는 주제를 삭제하거나 새로운 주제를 추가하세요.
and ensure you've got a solid outline before creating a presentation.
프레젠테이션을 만들기 전에 탄탄한 개요가 있는지 확인하세요.
Managing your inbox can feel like a full-time job.
받은 편지함을 관리하는 일은 풀타임 직업처럼 느껴질 수 있습니다.
Today, a new inbox is here.
오늘은 새로운 받은편지함이 왔습니다.
Introducing Prioritize My Inbox.
받은 편지함 우선순위 지정을 소개합니다.
Let's look at this email from a new customer.
새로운 고객의 이메일을 살펴보겠습니다.
When you select it, Copilot shows you why it thinks it's significant
이를 선택하면 Copilot에서 해당 항목이 중요하다고 생각하는 이유를 보여줍니다.
and highlights what action you need to take.
그리고 어떤 조치를 취해야 하는지 강조 표시합니다.
This is a key customer for the next few months,
이는 향후 몇 달 동안의 핵심 고객입니다.
so you teach Copilot that all emails mentioning them are top priority.
그래서 Copilot에게 그들이 언급된 모든 이메일이 최우선 순위라고 가르쳐 주게 됩니다.
We're enabling every organization to break free
우리는 모든 조직이 자유로워질 수 있도록 지원합니다.
of yesterday's take on business process.
어제의 비즈니스 프로세스에 대한 견해입니다.
Copilot agents supercharge every business process.
부조종사 에이전트는 모든 비즈니스 프로세스를 엄청나게 가속화합니다.
You can create an agent with a single click
한 번의 클릭으로 에이전트를 생성할 수 있습니다.
from any SharePoint site, library, or folder.
모든 SharePoint 사이트, 라이브러리 또는 폴더에서.
In just a few seconds,
단 몇 초 만에,
your Copilot agent is ready to be used or shared with others.
귀하의 Copilot 에이전트는 다른 사람과 사용하거나 공유할 준비가 되었습니다.
Let's add it to your team chat so everyone can work with the agent.
모든 사람이 에이전트와 협력할 수 있도록 팀 채팅에 추가해 보세요.
Now, all those artifacts in SharePoint
이제 SharePoint의 모든 아티팩트
are immediately accessible and useful,
즉시 접근 가능하고 유용합니다.
so Copilot can reason over all the relevant content
그래서 Copilot은 모든 관련 콘텐츠를 추론할 수 있습니다.
to find what your team needs.
팀에 필요한 것을 찾아보세요.
Wow, there you have it.
와, 이제 다 봤습니다.
This is just the beginning of Wave 2,
이것은 단지 Wave 2의 시작일 뿐입니다.
and we're just getting started.
그리고 우리는 이제 막 시작일 뿐입니다.
I cannot wait to see what you do with all these new capabilities.
여러분이 이 모든 새로운 기능으로 무엇을 할지 기대됩니다.